RESUME

Monu Sagar

Email ID : monusagar250@gmail.com

Street no. c3, Iedgah road Subhash Nagar, jwalapur Haridwar Uttarakhand-249407

Mobile number-7668931282



Summary:

I am a capable goal oriented leader with strong communication skills working at improving health through yogic practices. I have worked as a yoga teacher in Bharat Thakur Artistic Yoga, for 6 years at Delhi, Mumbai and Dubai, teaching effective ways to understand the mind and body connection for physical, emotional and psychic growth for a healthier mind and body.

In Present I am working with Bharat Thakur Artisitic Yoga Companey.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

Academic

>	Teachers Training in Hatha Yoga	Yoga Shala Rishikesh	Feb. 2016
A	Theology Beautician Course	DSVV University Haridwar She's Beauty Parlour	Dec 2004 2007-2008
>	Graduation	B.A. English ,Eco ,sociology HNB Garhwal	2001-2004
>	12 th	VMIC SEC 1,BHEL HARIDWAR	2000-2001
>	10 th	VMIC SEC 5,BHEL HARIDWAR	1997-1998

Additional Knowledge:

Basic Knowledge of Comupter.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACHIEVEMENTS

- > Presented school parade as a commander and guide coutinuous years.
- Participated in school cultural activities.

Professional Experience

Yoga Teacher: Freelancer yoga trainer Dec 2015-March 2019

Senior Yoga Teacher: BTAY – Delhi, Mumbai, Dubai Dec 09 – Aug 2015

Senior Yoga Teacher: Life Style Yoga Dubai Sept 2015–Dec 2015

Beautician: She's Beauty parlour July 07 – July 08

LINGUIST PROFICIENCY:

• English & Hindi.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Practicing and Teaching Yoga
- Reading
- Dancing
- ➤ Listening to Music
- > Studying new facts on nutrition and health

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Date of Birth : 02-12-1979

Gender: Female

Father's Name: Mr. Ram Pal Sagar

Marital status = Unmarried

Nationality = Indian.

Date:

Place: (Monu Sagar)

